[Music]
[Música]
to the
a la
page
página
[Music]
[Música]
china
china
what's up
qué pasa
yes
sí
say I
yo digo yo
[Music]
[Música]
not even to walk
tampoco a caminar
marí marí
marí marí
friend
amigo
[Music]
[Música]
chetumal
chetumal
with
con
the quality whether weak and apathetic
la calidad ya sea débil y apática
gloves to love she will be more it
guantes a amar ella estará más
's me for Christmas
soy yo por la navidad
for me my sister karma
para mí mi hermana karma
cadiz to the yuca identity
cádiz a la yuca identidad
the fifth already for a callus
la quinta ya por un callo
danica talk
danica hablar
tasty for the quality anomaly
sabroso por la calidad anomalía
paris
parís
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
the studies were yorbis to party
los estudios fueron yorbis a partido
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
a glass for tabla
una copa para tabla
and canada
y canadá
[Music]
[Música]
low
baja
like this when the minimum of the demand goes in
así cuando el mínimo de la demanda va en
deceased
fallecida
[Music]
[Música]
fell the typical talk
cayó la típica hablar
anita does not
anita no
vary
varía
[Music]
[Música]
and
y
sandy
sandy
[Music]
[Música]
ferrari is the music that has come out already
ferrari está la música que ha salido ya
see the same list as always but  it's
ver la misma lista de siempre pero está
real and it's so early yes so early
real y está tan temprano si tan temprano
so early because we have things to
tan temprano porque tenemos cosas de las
talk about we have the gentleman I want to
que hablar tenemos al señor me quiero
update with the salsa at night
actualizar con el salsa de por la noche
if something strong comes out then at night
si sale algo fuerte luego por la noche
from another live several families
de otro directo varias familias
if another live comes out then at night
si sale otro directo luego por la noche
hey why does it say why does it say 0
oye porque pone porque pone 0
viewers
espectadores
and because the color of the camera has moved
y porque se ha movido el color de la
and I've gone
cámara y se me ha ido
well like this is halfway good Elisa is not
bueno así está medio bien no está elisa
the scoreboard but it's not 100 because it
el marcador pero es que no el 100 porque
updated the viewer scoreboard let's see I
actualizó el marcador de espectadores a
know that until now there will be fewer
ver sé que hasta ahora va a haber menos
people than at night
gente que por la noche
how can you do it I don't know thank you very much
como puedes realizarlo no sé muchas
son
gracias hijo
welcome to lata
bienvenido a lata
viewers
espectadores
update the cache
actualizar la caché
you know the hate comes out zero it doesn't take a
sabes el odio sale cero no se tarda un
while but there's nobody in tweets there's
rato pero no hay nadie en tweets
nobody I'm alone it won't be anymore in
no hay nadie estoy solo no estará más en
our 1080 already it's that I have to I have to
nuestra 1080 ya ya es que tengo que
configure it still done well I
tengo que configurar todavía hecho bien
have to
tengo que
tell you one thing although I can't say
deciros una cosa aunque no puedo decir
much about water I can't say much but I
mucho de agua no puedo decir mucho pero
have to say one thing
tengo que decir una cosa
yesterday I joined tattooing
ayer me sumé tatuando
yesterday I had this when all day that's
ayer me tuve está cuando todo el día por
why I wasn't here
eso no estuve aquí
bankia or banking impressive god
bankia o banca impresionante dios me
fixed my old tattoos and I finally
arregló los tatuajes viejos y por fin
have them all in  conditions god
los tengo todos en condiciones dios
finally I have everything everything is here for me
por fin lo tengo todo me está todo aquí
to your honor in this little space that I had
a la señoría en este huequito que me
left we had put the lady hurt
quedaba habíamos puesto a la señor hería
televisions to the ceo
teles al ceo
but finally I have everything well all in good
pero por fin tengo todo bueno todos en
condition yet we don't have to go over
condiciones todavía no hay que repasar
the prt this one has to be fixed the
el prt este hay que arreglarlo el
dog that has to be fixed and this arm
perrete que arreglarlo y este brazo el
next month what to fill but but they are
mes que viene ya lo que llenar pero pero
going to look super handsome all of these been
van quedar súper guapos todos estos sido
when he fixed them he had them in a
cuando me los ha arreglado los tenía
bad state he had them
fatal
without color half colored the
los tenía sin color a medio colorear el
control was pitiful and he put it
mando estaba lamentable y lo ha puesto
in good condition there we put
en condiciones por ahí le hemos puesto
a little star on it it looks quite here
una estrellita ya queda bastante acá
quite cool
bastante cool
although it is quite cool
aunque da bastante cool
the camera only moves the goddesses get
la cámara se mueve sólo las diosas se
tattoos for the salsa viva salsa steele sal
tatúa por la salsa viva salsa steele sal
okay don't make a mistake
se vale no se equivoque
well I saw that there was some salcedo
bueno he visto que había algún salcedo
from last night I'm going to update I deleted
de anoche me voy a actualizar he borrado
the previous live I explain why I
el directo anterior explicó porque he
deleted the previous live because
borrado el directo anterior porque
honestly watching it because of how much I
sinceramente viéndolo por lo harto ayer
had it yesterday yesterday I was putting my mind to
lo tuve ayer estuve poniendo mente
thinking with boredom I was I was
pensando con el aburrimiento
wrong I was a little
estaba equivocado estaba un poco
wrong in the live honestly
equivocado en el directo sinceramente
okay I gave a lot of importance to the
vale le di mucha importancia a la broma
blonde's joke and actually talking about it
del rubio y en realidad hablándolo
too in  house and so on
también en casa y demás
javi is all paulo
javi se está toda paulo
the fragile and possesses the blond sun joke
la frágil y posee la broma de sol rubio
is [ __ ] really what do
es una gilipollez en verdad qué pensáis
you think is scratching my zero equity
ustedes me está rayando el cero equity
it's [ __ ] I'm really here the
es una gilipollez yo está realmente la
blond joke
broma del rubio
if it's to wind herself and not even the
si a la propia wind y ni siquiera el
annoying one and
molesto
the truth is although I do give my
y la verdad aunque sí que luego doy mi
opinion later and my opinion is more objective
opinión y mi opinión es más objetiva
during the live it's true that there's a
durante el directo sí que es verdad que
moment when I give it a lot of importance
hay un rato de le doy mucha importancia
and it
y
can be misinterpreted
se puede malinterpretar
or the churra how are you do you remember me
o la churra cómo estás te acuerdas de mí
how have you been I'm a little sick today they
cómo has estado estoy algo enferma hoy
gave me three days off
me han dado tres días de descanso por
luckily it's not cobit kisses more cara
suerte no es cobit besazos más cara
because she told me that she was a little
porque me ha dicho que estaba algo
sick and that she sent 310 I say yes the one who
enferma y que mandó 310 digo si el que
sends the most a super chat to tell me that
más manda un súper cha para decirme que
in three days
te que en tres días
but I remember you I don't remember
pero me acuerdo de ti no me acuerdo de
you but I send you a hug thank you very much
ti pero te mando un abrazo muchas
for the super chat it
gracias por el super chat
's [ __ ] the blond joke is
es una gilipollez la broma del rubio es
[ __ ] I
una gilipollez
mean I set myself I set myself as an
o sea yo me puse yo me puse con el
example that it was done to him I will make that
ejemplo de que se le hiciera me haré esa
fortune for the joke because if god the
fortuna a la broma porque si dios el
water it's not the same it's not the
agua es que no es lo mismo no es lo
same I've been I've been reviewing
mismo he estado he estado repasando por
a bunch of my videos about windows and such this morning
la mañana un montón de los vídeos míos
and some unworthy person was harassed so it's
y un indigno fue acosada así que es
true that it's true that they
verdad que sí que es verdad que le
gave her a lot they gave her a lot of stick when
dieron mucho le dieron mucha caña cuando
in the times when she started they
en los tiempos en los que ella empezó le
gave her a lot of stick for [ __ ] like
dieron mucha caña por gilipolleces o sea
because she uploaded a video with him greg
porque subió un vídeo con él greg
giving him a thumbnail a kiss in the
dándole una miniatura un besito en la
thumbnail and it's like people throwing
miniatura y es como la gente lanzándole
too much hate at him that's why I've always
demasiado odio por eso eso siempre lo he
said that but harassment wasn't sent to her
dicho pero acoso tampoco le mandaron
either I mean there was also a bit of give and
o sea hubo también un poco de toma y
take to windows live the thing also
daca a windows live el rollo también de
that the blond was pulling her hair no it wasn't
que el rubio le tirara pullita no no era
one thing man one thing it's something bigger
una cosa tío una cosa es algo más grande
and more serious in fact well let's see
y más grave de hecho bueno vamos a ver
today here on wind and they're giving them a
hoy aquí en wind y les está dando un
little bit of vollard wing but it's not like it's
poquito de vollard ala pero tampoco es
giving her much
que le está dando mucho
for that thank you very much
para eso muchas gracias
jesus thank you very much
jesus muchas gracias
nothing god the horns of nasa or well
nada dios los cachos de la nasa o bien
sincerely I
sinceramente
think that in the south chat they
creo que en el chat del sur te
criticized you for that opinion I have
criticaron por esa opinión
n't seen I've seen I've seen almost but
no he visto he visto he visto casi pero
like many times disgusting people come to me
como muchas veces me vienen gente
and many people  well we do not
asquerosa y mucha gente pues nosotros no
take into account they should put it in the
tengo en cuenta lo deben poner en los
comments you know I do
comentarios sabe
not take into account the comments
no tengo en cuenta los comentarios
because when the subject is there
porque cuando el tema está la viene
many unfortunate people many haters let's
mucha gente lamentable muchos haters a
see but man reviewing what I review
ver pero hombre revisando lo que revisa
my own videos and windy harassed it
mis propios vídeos y windy acosada no
was not, I mean on the part of ari it
fue o sea por parte de por parte de ari
was a give and take, I mean ar and said
fue un toma y daca osea ar y le dijo
ugly things to him and wind and said ugly things to him
cosas feas y wind y le dijo cosas feas
the photos collected in case someone
las fotos recopiladas por si alguien me
tells me that it would not be
dice que no
one or the other he would
sería una ni la otra
stay still neither one nor the other and
se estuviera quieto ni una ni la otra y
then with the issue of the blonde is that there is
luego con el tema del rubio es que hay
a video of wind and apologizing
un vídeo de wind y pidiéndole disculpas
to ruble is here look
al rublo está aquí mira
wind and he apologized to the blonde
wind y se disculpó con el rubio en el
last year
año pasado
the fight was for a long time and he never cut it
la pelea mucho tiempo y nunca la corte
now
ahora
god I do not understand why it is like this not him
dios no entiendo por qué es así no él
in a live to draw it it does not seem
en un directo a dibujarlo no me parece
very logical to me with h they ask he said
muy lógico con h piden dijo
for nike and paid him to organize that
por nike y le pagó para organizar ese
tournament three years ago
torneo de hace tres años
I had no proof of it and it was an
yo no tenía pruebas de ello y fue una
assumption which I thought or assumed
suposición la cual yo pensaba o asumía
was true the truth was in very bad
que era cierta la verdad fue de muy mal
taste of my father javier from his knife I
gusto de mi padre javier de su cuchillo
also live from gaming doing
también vivo de el gaming de hacer
streams  of advertising and that was a letdown
streams de la publicidad y eso fue bajón
and part of it was like breaking a
y parte fue como romper un código
secret code of influence he apologizes for
secreto de influencia le pide perdón por
that [ __ ] to Rubin it's like because he's been
esa [__] al rubin es como porque haya
making videos trying to make him look
estado haciendo vídeos intentando
bad he doesn't
dejarlo mal no
say it happens a lot with the blonde on
dice pasa muchas veces con el rubio en
many occasions he went too far and started
muchas ocasiones se pasó y se puso a
chasing him through Los Angeles I mean she's not
perseguirlo por los ángeles o sea no es
a harassed woman a person who
una mujer acosada una una persona que
is the blonde at an event there was
está el rubio en un evento había hacía
too much emphasis on the
demasiado hincapié en la tontería del
blonde's nonsense and barely says right dude this
rubio y apenas dice correcto tío en esta
time he's right the people who
ocasión tiene la razón la gente que más
criticize the most are right I mean she
critica tiene la razón ósea
's not a harassed woman a person who
no es una mujer acosada una persona que
is harassed is not found it's not that she's not
es acosada no se encuentra no es que no
found it's that she went looking for the
se encuentra es que fue a buscar al
blonde at an event and went chasing him
rubio a un evento y se fue a perseguirlo
throughout the event and the blonde was running away
por todo el evento y el rubio huyendo
and then he made a video throwing
y luego hizo un vídeo tirando a la
[ __ ] and then another one and I have seen it says apparently
[__] y luego otra y yo has visto dice
all the big ones are there I
por lo visto están todos los grandes ahí
saw it on Roberto Baquero's channel
lo vi en el canal de roberto baquero
recommended I don't know what you're talking about
recomendado no sé de lo que me hablas
Eloy what is a game an event
eloy qué es lo que es un juego un evento
what do I
que es lo que
have to tell you that I have many
tengo que deciros que tengo muchas
surprises I
sorpresas yo
have many surprises
tengo muchas sorpresas
wind and I didn't like her because she was a little
wind y me caía mal porque era un poco
annoying with the same thing  we
molesta con lo mismo
were milk we were milk I changed the
éramos lecha éramos lecha cambie la
category of tweets and the title but I know
categoría de tweets y el título pero sé
that I come across as spectators guys I don't know
que me salen ser espectadores tíos no sé
if there are people in your son no no it is not
si hay gente en tu hijo no
said people
no se dice gente
dallas said that rubí has ​​been harassing for years
dallas dijo que rubí lleva año acosando
unworthy
indigno
or rather a thing that gives the wants to play
o sea una cosa que da la quiere hacerle
a joke on the blond that you want a
una broma al rubio que le quieras un
troll or why
trole o por qué
because he wants to join the movement it is
porque se quiera sumar a la movida está
of the profit not totally legitimate that he
del rédito no totalmente lícito que se
wants to join
quiera sumar
for the moments
para los momentos
[ __ ] I don't know why I have
[__] yo no sé para qué tengo
moderators in tweets if every day I
moderadores en tweets si todos los días
have to get involved in changing this
me tengo que meter yo a cambiar esto
then in the end grandpa rolle player
entonces al final abuelito rolle player
and this who the [ __ ] well this title
y esto que quién [__] pues este título
the other day
el otro día
so I call him harassers
así que le llamo acosadores
rubén something wind and that mockery of them
rubén una cosa wind y esa burla de ellas
and wind and here you have asking him for
y wind y del aquí tenéis pidiéndole
forgiveness
disculpas
but the joke is [ __ ]
pero la broma es una gilipollez
apart from the fact that the clip apart from the fact that
aparte de que el clip aparte de que el
part of the foot was manipulated
clip parte del pie estaba manipulado
and he was referring to the chocas the
y se estaba refiriendo al chocas la
part where he says he wants to fight
parte en la que dice que quiere pelear
with win said [ __ ] apart from what
con win dijo una gilipollez aparte de lo
the blond says but let's  see it
que dice el rubio pero vamos a verlo
here in the video the gossip youtuber or in
aquí en el vídeo el chisme youtuber o de
fact it must
hecho
be yesterday between the
hay que ser el día de ayer entre de la
review rubios and in between wind yesterday
review rubios y de por medio wind ayer a
despite the fact that she did nothing this
pesar de que ella no hizo nada en esta
time do not approach well first of
ocasión no se acerque bueno primero que
all she uploaded them to her video on her
nada las subió a su vídeo a su canal de
youtube channel where at the beginning she mentions that
youtube en donde al inicio menciona que
indeed the followers of the
efectivamente que los seguidores del
rubio are covering up the clip where
rubio se están tapando el clip en donde
rubios himself mentions that he wants to
el mismo rubios menciona que quiere
fight a woman with winnie here that
luchar con una mujer con winnie here que
despite the fact that rubios himself vete a
a pesar de que el mismo rubios roo vete
hug
un abrazo
in that same clip he mentioned that he obeyed
en ese mismo clip mencionó que obedecía
as a joke but dallas mentions like these
de coña pero dallas menciones como éstas
javi quoted handsome and the troll or dallas
javi citó guapo y el trole o de dallas
was good but it was not such a
estuvo bueno pero no fue una broma tan
serious joke name the serious thing is that you
grave nombre lo grave que luego te lo
take something like that seriously the
tomes en serio una cosa así
serious thing is that you take following
lo grave es que te tomes el seguir una
something like that even though it is a joke if
cosa así que a pesar que sea de broma si
he did it it would be too much that
él lo hiciera estaría de más que
canceled just a month ago rubios
cancelado hace sólo un mes el rubios
said live that he would hit wind
dijo en directo que él le pegaría a wind
and that he would be the only person with whom he would
y que sería la única persona con la que
sit her down in a fight is that he would
la sentaría un combate es que él le
hit wind and call or make a  intro
pegaría a wind y llama o hace una intro
seriously does a serious intro just
en serio hace una intro seria hace sólo
a month ago rubio said that he would hit
un mes rubio dijo que él le pegaría
windy and there would be a debate a debate not
windy y las estaría un debate un debate
a fight he doesn't say that le ruiz
no un combate no dice que le ruiz nos
tells us that he would hit windy and for dioxide
dice que le pegaría wind y por dióxido
the one who for god
el que por dios
the one who out of hate
el que por de odio
if he wants to pass me
si quiere pasar conmigo
if wind and wants to hit me in the
si wind y se quiere pegar conmigo en el
context of ibai's evening
contexto de la velada de ibai
and the worst thing is not that
y lo peor no es eso
the worst thing is that it is perfectly understood I
lo peor es que se entiende perfectamente
prepare myself it would be the only thing that
me preparo sería lo único que
if she proposes a fight she
si ella le propone un combate ella
would accept it is [ __ ] it
aceptaría es una gilipollez
is [ __ ]
es una gilipollez
and then later on in the click it
y luego encima más adelante en el click
may exist half but then later on
podrá existir medio pero luego más
in the click the rubio says the
adelante en el clic el rubio dice lo
worst thing is that she would cure me juan
peor es que ella me curaría a mí juan
cala thank you very much a hug laugh
cala muchas gracias a un abrazo reír
aside after that he says it
aparte después de que después dice que
's a joke but he loves you he needs to
es broma pero te quiera hace falta que
say it
lo diga
is that he doesn't need to say it and in
es que no hace falta que lo diga y en
dallas in his live and in the video well I do
dallas en su directo y en el vídeo bueno
n't know if in the video at that part he
no sé si en el vídeo por esa parte se
starts to say it and he doesn't say it as a joke and he doesn't
pone a decir y no lo dice de broma y no
say it as a joke there he
lo dice de broma
clearly said that he is going to break his
hay claramente dijo que le va a partir
face in a threat
la cara en una amenaza
santiago thank you very much for  renew
santiago muchas gracias por renovar
the family I
la familia no
have no origin
tengo origen
thinking it would be fight of the year that would be
pensando sería combate del año eso sería
fight of the year
combate del año
off
apagado
and he started making jokes about how you would
y se puso a hacer bromas sobre cómo
define and jokes about how to hit
definirías y bromas sobre cómo pegarle
a girl who is 20 centimeters tall and this
una chica que mide 20 centímetros y esta
part when Dallas uploads this video he already
parte cuando dallas sube este vídeo ya
knows
sabe
that the video was manipulated
que ese vídeo estaba manipulado
so the worst thing that I see here is that
entonces lo peor que yo veo aquí es que
he knows that the video is manipulated
él sabe que ese vídeo está manipulado
the worst thing is that I don't know if I have
lo peor es que no sé si tengo
the worst that this affects his work
lo peor que esto afecta a su trabajo
and if he has been since 2019 2020 [ __ ]
y si lleva desde el 2019 2020 de [__]
great that I am [ __ ] great
madre que ando de [__] madre
looking to clean up your image baltasar
buscando limpia tu imagen baltasar
thank you very much and he was getting it
muchas gracias y lo estaba consiguiendo
and nothing more than there were four
y nada más que quedaban cuatro
[ __ ] left jong nam here there were four
[__] jong nam aquí quedaban cuatro
[ __ ] who were throwing at Dallas but
[__] que le tiraban a dallas pero
literally 4 [ __ ] who looked
literal 4 [__] que se veían
ridiculous if they do these things they
ridículo si hacen estas cosas te
harm yourself god
perjudican a ti mismo dios
is literally here there is someone is that I
está literalmente por aquí hay alguien
was watching this yesterday with the
es que esto lo estaba viendo ayer con el
time that I had in the I don't know he recorded it
tiempo que tuve en el no sabe lo grabó
in a live before but the video is
en un directo antes pero el video está
edited and the video is uploaded the
editado y el vídeo está sube al día
next day and here at the end of the live
siguiente y aquí al final del directo
someone tells him but  the video is
alguien le dice pero el video está
edited
editado
[ __ ] the ddi will be the same with what he says
[__] la ddi será igual con lo que dice
at the beginning it's enough we don't care
al principio es suficiente no nos da
don't make an intro at the beginning
igual no haga una intro al principio
super serious saying that the blond
super serio diciendo que el rubio ha
said he would hit him windy and what and what I
dicho que le pegaría windy y qué y qué
joke about how he would hit him I do
gasto broma de cómo le pegaría
n't see it here here from where it comes from
no lo veo aquí aquí a partir a proviene
the distance of my arms I wouldn't let him
la distancia de mis brazos no le dejaría
see at any time I would be hitting
ver en ningún momento estaría golpeando
the
el
funny one I'm going to hit a woman 20
gracioso ando con pegarle a una mujer 20
centimeters smaller than your jeans
centímetros más pequeña que tus vaqueros
or etc you
o etc
touch I think I've never seen but
tocas yo creo que no he visto nunca pero
the joint the other day was even
el porrito del otro día fue hasta
funny it came out doggy style I laughed
gracioso salió colo del perrito me reí
because the older one doggy style isn't
porque el mayor del perrito no está
affecting anyone but it's that here what do you
afectando a nadie pero es que aquí que
want them to call the blond an abuser
quieres que llamen al rubio maltratador
or an aggressor of women or something like that
o agresor de mujeres o algo por el
god
estilo dios
I don't know it seems that it seems that if it seems
yo no sé parece que parece que si parece
that what he wants is for others to
que lo que quiere es que a los demás los
call them an abuser call him what he
llamen maltratador lo llamen tal qué
wants like
quiere como
in revenge what happened to him in
en venganza lo que le ha pasado a él en
revenge what happened to him he wants
venganza lo que le ha pasado a él quiere
everyone everyone else to also
que a todos a todos los demás también lo
call them abusers pedophiles I don't know what
llames maltratadores pedófilos no sé qué
and that's an idea that  you have to
y eso es una idea que se tiene que
get it out of your head because they
quitar de la cabeza porque es que
literally are not going to cancel rubio
literalmente no van a cancelar a rubio
that's why that click
por eso es por ese clic
is hurting himself and more
se está perjudicando el a sí mismo y más
when everyone knows that it is a
cuando todo el mundo sabe que es un clic
manipulated click no longer
manipulado ya no no
seems illogical to me that they do not melt it to
me parece ilógico que no se lo funden a
rubios for that nonsense
rubios por esa tontería
short avoid being short you will be very agile
bajito evite ser bajito será muy ágil la
short people are usually much more
gente baja es suele ser muchísimo más
agile than tall people periodically I
ágil que la gente alta periódicamente me
get like that
pongo así
and it is that I mean you can't do anything if
y es que o sea no puede hacer nada si el
rubio can make a joke about how he would
rubio puede gastar una broma de cómo se
fight him clash he can make
pelearía con él choca la puede gastar
a joke because I know how he
una broma de porque sé de cómo se
would fight with whitney it is that it is more look thinking about it I
pelearía con whitney es que es más mira
was already in my head I
dándole vuelta estaba ya en la cabeza
was thinking
estaba pensando
well what if wind and had made the joke
bueno y si wind y hubiera hecho la broma
with rubio that he would challenge him to a
con el rubio de que lo retaría un
fight of
combate
course it is a nice little joke but if he
claro es una bromita linda pero si eso
does that from Dallas he would already be canceled and look how
lo hace de dallas ya estaría cancelado y
difficult it is to cancel dallas saying
mira que es difícil cancelar a dallas a
saying of the reason
decir a diciendo de la razón
desire of the reason if that joke but there is
deseo de la razón si esa broma pero ahí
no fault of the rubio it is not to blame
no tiene culpa el rubio no tiene culpa
people with the double standard no
la gente con la doble vara de medir no
that is totally true is if dallas
que es totalmente cierto es si el dallas
makes that joke
hace esa broma
with  someone would already be calling him an
con alguien ya le estarían llamando
abuser and all things
maltratador y todas cosas
but the ruber hasn't done it
pero el ruber no lo ha hecho
man if I tell you that he just talks to me
tío si os cuento que me acaba habla
but rugby has also put [ __ ]
pero el rugby también ha metido [__]
about Dallas or I mean he stays he can say what he
de dallas o sea queda la puede decir lo
wants he can take it seriously or not it is not
que quiera puede tomárselo serio o no
known why he said everything without
tampoco se sabe por qué lo dijo todo sin
Rubio it can be they will interpret us I can't
rubio se puede van a interpretar
tell us but if I can
no nos lo puedo decir pero si yo puedo
say that
decir que
I have some projects
tengo unos proyectos
and I have some invitations to things that have been
y tengo unas invitaciones a cosas que me
made to me that the day that I am going to
han hecho que el día que os lo voy a ir
tell you about it obviously
contando evidentemente
in a few hours I will tell you a
en pocas horas os cuento una
powerful
potente
powerful proposal that I already have many very
potente que ya tengo muchas propuestas
powerful proposals action
potentísima acción
in the next few months
en los próximos meses
in made in the next few hours I
en hechas en las próximas horas os
will tell you one that can go well it can
cuento una que puede salir bien puede
go wrong I don't know maybe I'm bad at it
salir mal no sé a lo mejor se me da mal
I want to know
quiero saber
in the most wants to invest in three to the
en los más quiere invertir en tres al
SEO
seo
today that today Wednesday tomorrow Friday I will
hoy que hoy miércoles mañana el viernes
tell it on Friday
lo cuento
afternoon we will see each other here
el viernes por la tarde nos vemos aquí
until now okay do you think
hasta ahora vale os parece
Friday afternoon we will see it here be
el viernes por la tarde lo vemos aquí
careful I understand that they don't do it because it is
ojito entiendo que no lo hacen porque es
him but it is different when it is another
él pero es diferente cuando es otra
person although it is nonsense but for
persona aunque es una chorrada pero por
nonsense they also cancel
chorradas también cancelan
socas I invite you to his house
socas te invito a su casa
[Laughs]
[Risas]
nothing
nada
the distance my arms wouldn't let him
la distancia mis brazos no lo dejaría
see at any moment I mean he would be
ver en ningún momento o sea estaría
hitting constantly and he wouldn't be
golpeando de constantemente y no se
able to defend himself I mean that's why they have to
podría defender o sea es que lo tienen
do it not to put tall people
que hacer por eso no meter a gente alta
with short people because it's impossible
con gente baja porque es imposible al
totally disgusting taking into account
totalmente asqueroso tenido en cuenta
that the other way around like that the number one reason already
que al revés así la razón número uno ya
thing against the bng in recent Arab years
cosa contra el bng en los últimos años
is disgusting so I decided to play the
es asqueroso así que decidí jugarse la
intro I spoke to him with your help and
intro le hablé con vuestra ayuda y
change his avatar for a big wind and
cambiar su avatar por un gran wind y
precisely to attention on that
para precisamente atención sobre ese
subject which his fans have
tema tema el cual sus fans han ocultado
completely hidden and problems precisely
por completo y problemas precisamente
that what someone
que lo que haga alguien aceptado
socially accepted does is accepted absolutely
socialmente se le acepta absolutamente
everyone can you imagine that in chos
todos os imagináis que en chos
congratulations to go your way with your
felicitaciones a ir por tu camino con tu
father just spoke to me and to know the
padre me acaba de hablar y saber la
person who is speaking to me right now Isabel
persona que me habla ahora mismo isabel
the
la
director
directora
of Federico's program
del programa de federico
uncle is scratching me a lot the zero in
tío me está rayando mucho el cero en
tweet
tweet
some in which you can coincide with the
alguna en la que puedes coincidir con el
chocas 12 the choca where it doesn't feel
chocas 12 el choca donde no se siente
leave me alone I can't say the good I don't
dejarme en paz no puedo decir el bien no
say it
lo digo
windy was the one that bothered the blond the most let's
windy fue la que más molestó al rubio a
see
ver
at the beginning at the beginning of the movement
al principio al principio de la movida
and especially in general it is true
y sobre todo en general sí que es verdad
that she has been given a lot of stick wind and for
que se le ha dado mucha caña wind y por
little thing and salsa it will be a lot with her
poca cosa y salsa será mucho con ella
but as much as she is being harassed
pero tanto como que se le está acosando
as much as she is being harassed
tanto como que se le está acosando
if it occurred to me to joke about hitting
se me ocurriese bromear con pegarle a
a girl 20 centimeters and say a
una chica 20 centímetros y decir un
direct just like one is that they would do
directo tal cual la de una es que harían
to me and of course justified
a mí y por supuesto justificadísimas
because I would be the one if Dallas
porque sería yo el que si dallas
made a joke in which he made
hicieron una broma en el que él hiciera
him say well then I'm going to invite him to
que él dijera bueno pues voy a invitar a
a
un combate a
chicken fight would I accept a fight let's see some
pollo aceptaría un combate a ver alguna
girl with whom he has fought true on the
tía con la que se haya pelea verdad en
internet tell me some girl
internet decirme alguna tía
and everything thank you very much king
y todo muchas gracias rey
according to some
según alguna
some days life is already
algunas día la vida las ya te está
blocking you ok no but it won't take long well I
bloqueando ok no pero no tarda pues
hope not because I would agree with
espero que no porque le daría la razón a
many people then
mucha gente entonces
man no clear example honey is not
hombre no claro ejemplo de miel no es
with anyone
con nadie
I put you know the
pongo sabes la
coronary something clear imagine that
coronario algo claro imaginaros que
Dallas says I would accept a fight of
dallas dice yo aceptaría un combate de
argem plate
argem plate
people would form it directly
la gente lo formaría directamente
or with arrolla
o con arrolla
people would form it but I would defend it
la gente lo formaría pero yo lo
I would say  I would say because of all the [ __ ]
yo diría yo diría por menuda gilipollez
the truth is
la verdad
that the challenges debate yes well whatever it is whatever it is
la que los retos debate sí bueno la que
yes
sea la que sea la que sí
[Laughs]
[Risas]
whatever but I will make an example of the
la que sea pero me haré ejemplo en lo
same
mismo
disgusting however the blonde can not
asqueroso sin embargo el rubio no puede
say with impunity because he is the blonde
decir impunemente porque es el rubio
in front of his fans they justify him and
ante sus fans lo justifican y me
end up attacking me too he
terminan atacando a mí también da las
puts them on twitter team and that you have
pone en twitter team y que tienes
problems without telling me that you have
problemas sin decirme que tienes
problems and in question is a comment
problemas y en cuestión es un comentario
where someone tells him bullets because you
en donde alguien le dice balas porque
are like that the blonde thing of wanting to hit
eres así lo de rubios de querer pegar a
wind and it is a joke just like you joking
wind y es una broma así como tú bromear
girls about hitting your sister because you know it would
tías con pegar a tu hermana porque sabes
never happen do not try to back down and
que nunca pasaría no trates de atrás y
see things also you say well blonde
verza las cosas además dices bien rubios
is the culprit of bullying wifi that is
es el culpable del bullying a wifi eso
false she humiliated herself with the
es falso ella misma se humilló con los
videos towards blondes but well in the same
vídeos hacia rubios pero bueno de igual
way winzip betrayed all this after
forma winzip traicionó a todo esto tras
the tweets that the same one of
los tweets que había puesto el mismo de
the review had put with the wind mural and
la review con el mural de wind y
putting an emoji of a monkey covering himself has
poniendo emoji de un changuito tapándose
not given him much flattery windy or
no le ha dado mucha coba windy o sea
wind and right now he is in a period and
wind y ahora mismo está en una época y
the other day  we saw it I uploaded a video
el otro día lo vimos subí un vídeo
chuck and thank you very much a big kiss and the
chuck y muchas gracias a un besote y el
other day we made a video on the
otro día hicimos un vídeo en el canal
main channel where we more or less analyzed
principal donde más o menos analizamos
well what wind is doing and now
bueno lo que está haciendo wind y ahora
not and wind and now he is dedicating himself to a he
no y wind y ahora se está dedicando a un
has a new channel that does like
tiene un canal nuevo que hace como
coldplay he uploads music videos he is with his fan he
coldplay sube videoclips está con su fan
is in another roll wind and has returned with
está en otro rollo wind y ha vuelto con
a new identity okay
una nueva identidad vale
and wind and right now I think he is in
y wind y ahora mismo yo creo que está en
a phase where he does not want he does not want
una fase de que no quiere no quiere
problems or controversy and he wants to
problemas ni quiere polémica y quiere
return to the internet in another way with another
volver a internet de otra forma con otro
roll okay and he does
rollo vale
not give it much attention so it is true
y no la da mucha bola así que es verdad
that I put it
que la puesto
and he has answered the two routes
y ha contestado a los dos trayectos
where the cartoon has
donde el dibujito
always supported me without asking for anything in
siempre me ha apoyado sin pedir nada a
return dalas is an angel
cambio dalas es un ángel
but of course here wind and in what
pero claro aquí wind y en lo que quiere
they want their role that everyone
ellas su rol de que todo el mundo la
is harassing her and that she is no longer successful
está acosando y de que ya no tiene éxito
in the networks or numbers or anything because there are
en las redes ni números ni nada porque
votes of the majority
hay voto de los más
and to give it for the she was giving like to
y darla por la estaba dando like a
tweets like this hater denunciations to
tweets como este hater denuncias a
dallas percent of what I have to tell you
dallas por ciento de lo que os tengo que
of course two things
por supuesto dos cosas
outside of the whole roll
fuera parte ya de todo el rollo
was the part of  this whole thing
fue la parte de todo el rollo este que
we're talking about, what's
estamos hablando no
not good is that they report him and
lo que tampoco bien es que le reporten y
the accounts to Dallas,
las cuentas al dallas
that they don't deport them in the twist to Dallas
que no les deporte en el twist a dallas
as they were organizing to
como se estaban organizando para
report his tweet, nor do I
reportarle el tuit ni tampoco
see it as normal that they took down
veo normal que le hayan tumbado el
Wind's instar if
instar a wind if
when it's literally no longer
cuando literalmente ya no tiene la culpa
Dallas's fault that brought up the subject
que dallas haya sacado el tema
or that Wind defended him and because he
dallas o lo defienda wind y porque él
knows that Wind and has contact with him,
sabe que wind y tiene contacto con él
well, he
los más
came from today searched, ying, it makes
pues viene de hoy cacheado ying tiene
sense, the truth is, it makes
lógica la verdad
sense, no, let's see, we're
tiene lógica no a ver es que estamos
talking about serious things, man, and that
hablando de cosas serias tío y
's precisely what I'm telling you,
precisamente es lo que te digo
precisely what we're defending
precisamente lo que estamos defendiendo
is that people are not slandered and
es que a la gente no se le calumnia y
that people are not defamed and such, you know,
que la gente no se le difama y tal sabe
within the criticism, of course, you
dentro de por supuesto la crítica tú
can criticize him and hey, for example,
puedes criticarlo y oye por ejemplo
certain ones would have said them, well, I think
cierta las hubiera dicho pues me parece
the joke that Rubio Windy made is really bad, well, Dallas
muy mal la broma que le ha hecho rubio
using Wind and for his
dallas usando a wind y para sus peleas
personal fights every 10, no, let's see, if you
personales cada 10 no a ver es que si tú
want to get into the troll joke or the
quieres entrar en la broma del trole o
network and wants to troll Leal Rubio, delete
de red y quiere trolear leal rubí borrar
the drawing and such  by the end if it is it
el dibujo y tal para el final si es lo
is even funny that is what
es incluso divertido es de lo que trata
the war is about but man already accusing him of
la guerra pero hombre ya acusarlo de
hitting women
pegar mujeres
accusing him of hitting women
acusarlo de pegar mujeres
and also in his live saying and he did not
y además en su directo diciendo y no lo
say it as a joke he did not say it as a joke yes I
dijo de broma no lo dijo de broma sí lo
said it as a joke hey then the joke
digo de broma oye que luego la broma
can be more accurate less accurate
puede ser más acertada menos acertada
well each one there
pues bueno cada uno allá
if it was funny he did not go informing
si fue divertido no se fue informando
Dallas will apologize for the
dallas se disculpara por el vídeo
edited video misinformed on this occasion I
editado mal informado en esta ocasión yo
think not
creo que no
on this occasion I think it is not
en esta ocasión yo creo que no
that Dallas skated twice in a
es que dallas a patinar ya dos veces en
row with those of Willy and in addition to the
seguida con los de willy y además del
blond symbol of Willis and those of
rubio símbolo de willis y los de
and those of Willy of believing it of the chick
y los de willy de creerlo del pollito
that that was even funny because that
eso eso fue hasta gracioso porque eso
was simply because he did not know the
fue simplemente porque no sabía el
context of how he had started the fight
contexto de cómo había iniciar la pelea
and such it is not to throw [ __ ] you understand
y tal no es por tirar [__] me entiende
but but to start saying when he is
pero pero ponerte a decir cuando el el
not stupid he
no es tonto
can have many things but so much he is not
puede tener muchas cosas pero tanto no
he knows that the video is a joke
él sabe que ese vídeo es de broma
and then in case he did not know because
y después por si no lo sabía porque yo
in the morning for example when I saw the
por la mañana por ejemplo cuando vi el
retweet that he made I did not know that the
retweet que él hizo yo no sabía que el
video was edited
vídeo estaba montado
when I saw this video with the cut
yo cuando vi el vídeo este con el corte
of  Rubio says back and I said
del rubio dice atrás y dije
in the morning
por la mañana
but then but then when they
pero luego pero luego cuando ya me
told me it was cut I was going well
dijeron que estaba recortado iba bueno
Javi you didn't send me you see me and I took it recently
javi no me mandaste me ves y tome
haha ​​you see audited thank you very much
reciento jaja ves auditó muchas gracias
for the super chat
por el super chat
I think wind and should have responded something
pienso que wind y debió responder algo
like don't get me involved in your shitty
así como a mí no me metan en sus [__]
fights I'm on my own but more
de peleas yo estoy a mi bola pero más
respectful obviously
respetuoso obviamente
because wind and the truth is he still has the
porque wind y en verdad tiene el
resentment
resquemor todavía
and the little obsession that wind has and he
y la pequeña obsesión que tiene wind y
understands me there's no
me entiende
video of Dallas where he says if he
no hay un vídeo de dallas donde dice si
were her boyfriend he would hit her if I've
fuera su novio la golpearía si lo he
seen it in the author's video it's the famous
visto en el vídeo del autor es el famoso
click that they put so much that it was like
click ese que ponen tanto que era como
the vitz the headquarters the villain meme what are you
el vitz la sede el meme del villano de
talking about if it was also a
de qué estás hablando si igual era una
joke that of course exactly the
broma eso claro exactamente
same that was a joke I would have
igual eso era una broma me hubiera
liked to make a more structured video
gustado hacer un vídeo más estructurado
on the subject for the main channel
sobre el tema para el canal principal
but no longer it's not anymore
pero ya no
days have passed I
ya no se han pasado días ya no
would not have liked to make a video well
me hubiera gustado hacer un vídeo bien
but it was the video that played yesterday already today
pero era el vídeo que tocó ayer ya hoy
not to mention what he said about someone
no ni hablar de lo que dijo de alguien
play the game play that in what he said
play the game play que en lo que dijo
well what I say give and I used to create
bueno lo que digo dar y empleé que crear
harassment to  whitney photo maida castillo
el acoso a whitney foto maida castillo
of the two we have many videos no
de las dos tenemos muchos vídeos no
laughter also mentioned in his video
laughter también mencionó en su vídeo
amin author in his video
amin autor en su vídeo
I saw the least mentioned video
yo vi el vídeo menos mencionado
in what minutes
en qué minutos
and knows who it is xq dry is a
y sabe quién es xq se seque es un
streamer with a huge audience what
streamer con muchísima audiencia lo que
is number one
es el número uno
put his click with aura like that is rust and yes yes yes yes
puso clic suyo con aura así es óxido y
man clear well around the
sí sí sí sí hombre claro bueno por el
world you can use whatever you want
mundo puede usar lo que les dé la gana
of course and I'm yours
por supuesto y yo suyo
javi should have a talk with
javi debería de hacer una charla con
dallas and clarify the issue
dallas y aclarar el tema
he can come here whenever you want but
él puede venir aquí cuando quieras pero
what you want me to tell you neither in
lo que queréis que os diga tampoco en
clarifying he will know my personal opinion I have already
aclarar él sabrá yo mi opinión personal
said many times my opinion
ya lo he dicho muchas veces mi opinión
is that it was going [ __ ] great in 2019
es que iba de [__] madre en el 2019
even in 2020 and he has twisted it a lot he
incluso en el 2020 y lo ha torcido mucho
is twisting it if he doesn't realize he
lo está torciendo como no se dé cuenta
is twisting it
lo está torciendo
open live from telefé today well that's what
abra directo de telefé hoy pues eso
I intend samuel but you have some
pretendo samuel pero tengas unos
errands that's why I did this live
mandados por eso he hecho este directo
so early
tan temprano
and I will have to leave for two or three hours and
y tendré que salir dos o tres horas y
then at night when you come back and what I do
luego por la noche cuando vuelvas y lo
n't know what time but I will try to make
que no sé a qué hora pero intentaré que
it around 8  9
sea sobre las 8 9
what do you think happened for Dallas to
qué crees que pasó para que dallas
stop defending himself as it was I
dejará de defenderse como venía siendo
don't know if something has exploded in him
no sé si algo ha explotado en él
but he wears a regular grill go on he lets himself get
pero lleva una rejilla regulín
carried away by
dale se deja llevar mucho por las
emotions a lot I
emociones
don't know man but look at you
no sé tío pero fíjate tú
but I went to the tube and nothing, I mean with
pero fui a the tube que nada osea con
these things I think they hurt him
estas cosas yo creo que le perjudican
because in the end
porque al final
if you go staining your image with these
si vas manchando tu imagen con estas
things when you want to defend
cosas cuando te quieras defender de lo
yourself people are not going to be there they are not going to
tuyo la gente no va a estar no va a
be receptive to you okay it's late I'll
estar receptiva contigo vale es tarde os
pass it to you it
paso
may be late or it was
puede ser que tarde o fuera
the Chinese who made the weather
el chino que hizo clima
Dallas should turn the page and continue
dallas debería de pasar página y seguir
with his content and stop the controversy what I
con su contenido y que dejen la polémica
see is like a desire that
yo lo que veo es como unas ganas de que
like they have done to him that they
como a él se lo han hecho de que a todos
call everyone abusers and they
los llamen maltratadores y a todos los
call everyone farts and they call everyone I don't know
llamen pedos y a todos los llamen no sé
what it is like man don't go with that
qué es como hombre no vayas con esa
action if we are precisely
acción si precisamente estamos
defending that there is no slander and that he
defendiendo que no se calumnia y que nos
makes those types of accusations so
haga ese tipo de acusaciones tan a la
lightly man when there is evidence that there is
ligera hombre cuando haya pruebas de que
something true really really
hay algo de verdad de verdad de verdad
and if it is okay to put
y si está bien es poner
for what I tell you you have to  you have to get it
por lo que te digo tienes que tienes que
out of your head that they're going to jail
quitarte de la cabeza que van a cárcel a
everyone you have to get it out of your
todo el mundo te tienes que quitarte de
head that the blonde is going to be canceled
la cabeza que al rubio lo van a cancelar
that the blonde like that hits women no
que al rubio así que pega mujeres ni que
one and that they're going to take the
nadie y que se van a tomar en serio eso
combat tournament seriously please that they are the
del torneo del combate por favor que son
only ones they're going to take it seriously but the worst thing
solo van a tomar en serio pero lo peor
is that
es que
for me the worst apart from the fact that he's
para mí lo peor aparte de que se esté
hurting himself for me the worst thing
haciendo daño a sí mismo para mí lo peor
is that others existed
es que existieron otros
for nothing
para nada
and he knows that video is a joke and he knows
y él sabe que ese vídeo es de broma y él
that video isn't like that and he knows
sabe que ese vídeo no es así y sabe que
that video is [ __ ] you know that's the
ese vídeo es una gilipollez sabes eso es
worst thing I see important
lo peor que yo veo
family
familia
important family javier canijo
importante familia javier canijo el
Mr. tattoo well it looks beautiful
señor tatuaje bueno ha quedado precioso
my arm has been
mi brazo
reviewed they have all of them they have
me han repasado todos
fixed me because I had them let's say
me han arreglado porque los tenía vamos
half of each tattoo was missing but
faltaba la mitad de cada tatuaje pero
for a touch up everything had turned out
para un repaso había quedado todo
incredibly powerful and look at the bezel
increíblemente potente y mira el bisel
that you can see it
que se me está viendo
's also a gym because a
también es gimnasio porque viene
gym is coming to my house and
gimnasio en mi casa y sólo de pensar ya
just thinking about it the vice is already growing the next one we're going to fix is ​​the puppy the next one we're going to fix the puppy but first I'm going to fill this gap that I have here let's see if in the summer I'm good good  cool it's
a ver si en verano estoy bien bien chido
super cool the logo of the
está súper chulos el logo del logo de el
logo of the teles to the co2 the beticos over there
logo de teles al co2 los béticos por ahí
you'll see the logo of you have the ceo a little
verás el logo de tenés al ceo una
star
estrellita
especially aunt the remote man the flip I do
sobre todo tía el mando tío el flip hago
with that the remote the jagua podium the
con que el mando la de jagua podio
remote the remote was horrible the
el mando el mando estaba horrible el
remote was horrible
mando estaba horrible
and I had a trauma with the remote because
y yo tenía un trauma con el mando porque
a tattoo man something that you have on your
un tatuaje tío algo que tienes en la
skin and that you don't like and I had a
piel y que no te gusta y yo tenía un
trauma with the [ __ ] remote
trauma con el [__] mando
you know what it's like to have a tattoo or to
sabéis lo que es tener un tatuaje o que
look horrible
quede horrible
what do you want horrible and having money
qué quiere horrible y teniendo dinero
to get a good one
para hacerte uno bueno
having money to be you the good thing and
teniendo dinero para ser tú lo bueno y
that I went they did it to me horribly the remote
que fui me lo hicieron fatal el mando
[Music]
[Música]
and I thought it could not be fixed because I
y yo creía que no tenía arreglo porque
also went to get laser to erase
fui además a darme láser para borrar
it and I can't get laser because with
melo y no puedo darme láser porque con
the medication that I take with the chrome
la medicación que yo tomo con el chrome
like the photosensitive well I can't get
como el fotosensible pues no puedo darme
laser and then I already saw it screwed up and I
láser y entonces yo ya lo veía [__] y
had a trauma with the [ __ ] remote of
tenía un trauma con el [__] mando de
saying I'm going to tattoo my arm black
decir yo me voy a tatuar el brazo negro
just so you know because also in the
con tal de que sabe porque además en el
place you can see it and in the videos in the
sitio demás se ve y en los vídeos en el
place you can see it  and he fixes it for me or dude what a
sitio demás se ve y me lo arregla o tío
machine pastori what a
que máquina pastori
machine girl that gave me my period or in
qué máquina tía que me la regla o de
fact she had my eyes covered when she
hecho me tuvo los ojos tapados cuando lo
was fixing it javi told me I
fue arreglando me dijo javi lo he
managed to fix it and I bird and he wouldn't
conseguido arreglar y yo ave y no me
let me see what they support you it works the
dejaba ver lo que se te bancan trabaja
same and it's porous he didn't let me see it
igual y me está poroso no me dejó verlo
until I finished you know and when I
hasta que no termino sabes y cuando me
saw that there was a period that he had
vi que había regla que lo había
managed to fix it and wu under
conseguido arreglar y wu bajo
and the arm is missing a few
y el brazo le falta unos cuantos
details the little holes that you see they
detalles los huequitos que ustedes veis
will be putting little things to
se irán poniendo cositas pequeñas para
fill it completely
rellenarlo entero
and the dog fix it and something else around
y el perro arreglarlo y algo más por
here because here there is a gap too you know I
aquí que aquí hay un hueco también sabes
still have many holes left
todavía me quedan muchos huecos
pastorita you
pastorita tú
pastorita you in case you want to see the list
pastorita tu por si queréis ver la lista
and I recommend that if you go the
y yo recomiendo que si vos vayas el
tattoo is
tatuaje
worth the money that the
merece la pena el dinero que valga la
appointment is worth I brought it wait for an appointment whatever they
cita la traje espera para una cita lo
have because the skin in the end in the
que tengan porque la piel al final en la
skin man
piel tío
the skin in the skin
la piel en la piel
okay it's
vale
in Seville it's in Seville I
está en sevilla está en sevilla
had solved titsa no
había solucionado de titsa no
and I think the solutions never in
y creo que las soluciones nunca en la
life
vida
never in life I appeal the videos and
nunca en la vida yo apelo los vídeos y
apart from the worst thing is that the uncle  it doesn't
aparte de que lo peor es que el tito no
stop uploading because the videos of my
para de subir porque los vídeos de mis
text videos are super vivid
vídeos de textos están súper vidal
there are some with millions of
izados hay algunos con millones de
views okay they are super viral if it did
visitas vale están súper viralizado si
n't stop growing in followers in text
no paró de crecer en seguidores en texto
but the account is read-
pero la cuenta es tan solo de lectura
only read-only because well because I think there is
solo lectura porque pues porque yo creo
someone I have
que hay alguien
already found a contact on titov
ya he conseguido un contacto en titov me
a follower who works moderating
habló un seguidor que trabaja moderando
text spoke to me grandpa what a move
texto abuelo que movida
and he told me that it was very strange or rather that
y me dijo que era muy raro o sea que es
every day one throws me you
que cada día me tira uno
know for sure they will take it away from you at some
sabes seguro que te lo quitan en algún
point for sure but it's not normal for me
momento seguro pero no es normal lo mío
with the networks in the things that
con las redes en las cosas que a mí me
happen to me normal because there are people who are bad and
pasan normales porque hay gente mal y
are after me it
está detrás mío
's because there are people who are bad and are after
es porque hay gente mal y está detrás
me habit X-ray lamp is
mía hábito lámpara de rayos está
blinking imed anxiety me a little
parpadeando imed ansiedad a mí un poco
too but it's that I don't know what's wrong with it and I'm
también pero es que no sé qué le pasa y
not going to touch anything from this setup
ya no voy a tocar nada de este set up
that I already have left there are less here and
que ya me quedan hay menos aquí
sometimes
ya veces
well what happened because the
bueno qué es lo que ha pasado porque los
streams the other day when they were with
stream en el otro día cuando estaban con
the little war is on redit they started
la guerrita está de redit se pusieron a
asking for help from the armh and the beat ice
pedir ayuda a la armh y the beat ice
videos like beat and with this I'm
vídeos como beat y es que con esto tengo
afraid of the video of 8 radiant face with
miedo al vídeo de 8 cara radiante con
eyes  smiling radiant face with
ojos sonrientes cara radiante con ojos
smiling eyes dallas no well I'm not
sonrientes dallas no bueno ya no tengo
afraid anymore I don't give a damn about
miedo a mí me la suda
fear no I want them to upload kissing
miedo no yo quiero que los suba besarse
or in the end you know the only thing that
o al final sabe lo único que
is true
es verdad
a noise is playing in my pc you
está sonando un ruido en mi pc lo
hear it
escucha
why
por qué
and that noise that well it's like a
y ese ruido de que pues es como un
fan that is hitting something it's
ventilador que está dando con algo
true it
verdad
's like a lie hitting something now I did it it
es como mentira dando con algo ahora lo
's the fan that you're hitting
es el ventilador que estás dando con
something yes now you will see how I had to
algo si ahora lo veréis como lo tuve que
open it for the normal well not because he
abrir para el normal bueno no porque él
with him he gave it to me this so that it's not
me lo con él me lo de esto para que no
because he put it on me so that the
es porque él me lo puso para que el
computer wouldn't make any noise but
ordenador no hiciera nada de ruido pero
that's because I have had to take out and
eso es que yo como he tenido que sacar y
put back in the hard drive now when I
vuelve a meter disco duro ahora cuando
restored it I'm sure I left it
lo restaurados seguro que lo he dejado
wrong something good beat community and it is
mal algo bueno comunidad de beat y es
this is a call for leisure this is
this is a call por el ocio que esto es
a call for you time rush
una llamada para ustedes time rush
spanish streamer I am the blonde a
spanish streamer soy el rubio un
Spanish streamer we have a different
streamer español we have a diferentes
made in the past we have had
made in the past nosotros hemos tenido
our differences in the past but
nuestras diferencias en el pasado but
now I want to make an alliance ok but
now i want to make an alliance ok pero
now I need to ask for help ok
ahora necesito pedir las ayudas ok
oh wants to put beat and it's low cost ok
ay wants to put beat y es low cost ok
I want to put the logo of  beat 10
yo quiero colocar el logo de beat 10
videos low cost of the french fly on the
vídeos low cost of the french fly en la
flag of france
bandera de francia
and fix the pas doubts in delray displays
y fija el pas dudas en delray displays
ok great place and if you have questions
ok great place y si tú tienes dudas
if you have questions well here is the
si tú tienes dudas pues aquí está la
coordinate now yes I think it tells him
coordenada ahora sí creo que le dice
city doctors well this we will
médicos de ciudad pues this we will
stream of ned beatty that video
stream de ned beatty ese vídeo
the spanish streamers aurum play with
el de spanish streamers aurum play with
haiti thousand followers and by catch the
haiti mil followers y by catch the
biggest is telling them that they exempt him the
biggest les está diciendo que lo eximen
biggest in spain are going to recommend and they are
más grandes de españa van a recomendar y
going to provide it the videos the
van a proporcionarlo los vídeos the
beatles in exchange for helping them and see
beatles a cambio de que les ayude y ver
my
a mí
humble steinert rascal and second stream
humildes steinert bribón y second stream
vitis and fidel post every one tonic and
vitis y fidel post every one tonic y
because even when speaking the same
porque incluso que al hablar igual
what did we want to put mister
what did we want to put mister
destructor
destructor
videos with 1,010 this is a okay
vídeos con 1.010 this is a vale
the blond was going and also asked for attention
el rubio iba y también lo pidió atención
army of mts please help in the
ejército de mts por favor ayuda en el
replay in exchange they write the biggest
replay a cambio los escriben más grandes
in spain will broadcast in the next
de españa transmitirá en el próximo
single the beatles we are trying to
sencillo the beatles estamos tratando de
defend the community ready from the two
defender a la comunidad ready de los dos
french people who take up a lot of space let's
franceses que ocupan mucho espacio
paint
pintemos juntos
the stamps together and they listened to him
los sellos y le hicieron caso
two days without doing
dos días sin hicieron caso
host case and it's going to go have enjoyed it so
[__] y va a ir lo han disfrutado hasta
far we'll see
ahora lo vamos a ver
juan guarnizo also
juan guarnizo también
every day more bilingual sweating face
cada día más bilingüe cara sudando un
greetings man I understand a little I
saludo hombre yo entiendo un poco yo
understand a little
entiendo un poco
these guides are for exclusive use for me
estas guías son un uso exclusivo para mí
and bts is
y bts
not allowed to spread to another fandom
no se permite difundir para otro fandom
but the moments of my dog ​​​​want to
pero los momentos de mi perro quieres
go out to the terrace
salir a la terraza
is that until now
es que hasta ahora
at this time they like to be alone
a esta hora les gusta ponerse al solito
well they don't make a guide here and
bueno no se la hacen aquí una guía y
so on no but the bts beat and
demás no pero la comunidad bts beat y
kids community has canceled especially juan
kids ha cancelado sobre todo a juan
guarnizo but ibai is also worth
guarnizo pero a ibai también vale
especially playing uanl he released
sobre todo a jugar a uanl ha sacado
these tweets
estos tuits
there it doesn't open for me
ahí no se me abre
now
ahora
etc
etc
hahaha nothing against bts but in
jajaja nada en contra de bts pero de
fact it brightened my day the dancing chinese points
hecho me alegro el día los puntos chinos
are yours old well both this one from
son tuyas antiguos bueno tanto este de
that one is not that old but there are few and they
ese no es tan antiguo pero son pocos y
were canceling it hang on for that reason and he
lo estaban cancelando aguán por eso y
says wow but I don't know what
dice guau pero es que no sé qué
explanation they want it's a
explicación quieren es un tweet de
shitty tweet from 2020 things and
[__] del 2020 las cosas y las
mentalities change be it  god of
mentalidades cambiasso sea el dios de
2020 not even as if it were 2012
2020 tampoco como si fuera de 2012
if you know me the slightest bit you will be able to
si me conocen lo más mínimo podrán
notice it again sorry without more and
notarlo nuevamente perdón sin más y
wish and the same finally stop posting
desear y lo mismo por fin dejen de sacar
tweets from before things change
tweet de antes las cosas cambian
obviously it is annoying and we
obviamente es molesto y les pedimos
apologize but things are not like that anymore
disculpas pero las cosas ya no son así
yesterday I was talking until the end that
yo ayer estaba hablando hasta en el fin
the boys deserve a grammy and
de que los chicos se merecen un grammy y
all that
eso
plea of ​​looking for a man in a year and
pleitez de buscar hombre en un año y
a half
pico
in a year and a half well yes you can change your
en un año y pico bueno si puedes cambiar
mind yes well yes yes you can
de opinión si bueno sí si no puedes
change your mind
cambiar de opinión
no super super super super from one eczema
no super super super super de un eczema
to another in a year and a half like your
a otro en un año y pico
mentality your ideology and
en plan tu mentalidad tu ideología y
all that but man yes you can change your
todo eso pero hombre si puedes cambiar
mind
de opinión
but it was 2020 javi don't be
pero fue 2020 javi no te sorprendas
too surprised the weapons canceled a
mucho las armas cancelaron a una
singer just for talking to a
cantante solo por hablarle a una
singer she dances a [ __ ] she is an echo
cantante baila una chorrada es un echo
radilla the truth is
radilla la verdad
[ __ ] is closing the tab that I did not
a [__] es cerrar la pestaña que no
want to be the one who had to prepare
quería ser la que tenía preparar
cakes for the ceo
pasteles al ceo
I think Juan would change yes yes yes yes yes you
creo que juan cambiaría si si si si si
can change I have changed my
si puedes cambiar yo he cambiado de
mind on things in a year and on things
opinión en cosas en un año y en cosas
that I do yes yes you can change yes that is
que hago si si puedes cambiar si esa es
a tab  that I didn't want that ratio let's
una pestaña que no quería ese ratio
see if there's demand one thing that
a ver que hay demanda una cosa que ha
happened with ibai but I don't know if it's now is that
pasado con ibai pero no sé si es ahora
there's dancing they were throwing a
es que hay baile estuvieron tirando
lot at my age I
mucho a mi edad yo me
got a lot into salsa because
puse mucho en el salsero de eso porque
we were with I don't remember what things
estábamos con no me acuerdo qué cosas
yet but it's called k carnet or not
todavía pero se llama k carnet o no
canet or not
canet o no
here it's my turn to meta it has the name of a
acá me toca meta tiene nombre de
Doraemon character
personaje de doraemon
gameto
gameto
you get it out
you get it out
canelo came to your 'streaming' today yesterday kiss the
canelo came to your 'streaming' today en
best or streams orio carrera
yesterday kiss the best o streams orio
because it's always de streaming york
because it's always de streaming york
yesterday text reviews showroom play off
ayer texto reviews showroom play off
verify
verify
ibai father ando khan aqa mico is called
ibai padre ando khan aqa mico se llama
hecho here it's my turn to put in total that he has
hecho acá me toca meto en total que ha
received a lot of hate and vai from
recibió muchísimo odio y vai por parte
the French me and then here
de los franceses yo y entonces aquí por
apparently well he was there he talks a little about
lo visto pues iba ahí habla un poco de
what happened in these days in the last
lo que pasó en estos días en las últimas
hours I have
horas
read the four also that they have
he leído a los cuatros también que han
said that yesterday there was a lack of
dicho que ayer faltaba un poco de
representation from other streams
representación por parte de otros stream
it is from other communities also even
es de otras comunidades también incluso
from girls me people the truth is that the
de chicas yo gente la verdad que el
album that he thought before the public okay okay okay okay
disco que él pensaba ante público vale
this eternal of the
vale vale vale vale esto eterna del
album what was done is this is because the fans of the
disco lo hecho es esto es porque los fan
crash they've been throwing it
del choque han estado tirándole
because the camera moves by itself dude
porque la cámara se mueve sola tío
you see how the camera moves by itself on a
veis como la cámara se mueve sola en un
shitty tripod that moves alone I
trípode de [__] que se mueve solo
always have things more to dude elche
siempre tengo las cosas más al tío elche
tired I'm tired god I want to do
cansado estoy cansado dios quiero hacer
my salsa calm
mi salsero tranquilo
family this is because the
familia esto es porque los fans del
chocas fans were yesterday throwing it in his face and
chocas estaban ayer echándole en cara y
bye
bye
that they hadn't invited chocas to the redit thing
que no habían invitado a lo de redit al
okay and this is the explanation that is so
vale y esta es la explicación que es tan
device the only person left
device la única persona que quede
was really with silicon and I thought
realmente fue con silicio y yo pensaba
that whoever wanted to was coming in and out
que iba entrando y saliendo quien quería
okay I also thought that somehow it
vale también pensé que de alguna manera
was a little uncomfortable for some stream to
era un poco incómodo para algún stream
get into that call because there were 14 of us and there was
entrar en esa llamada porque éramos 14 e
even one time I went
incluso había alguna vez me volví a la
crazy I don't know if it happened to you you know that there
cabeza loca no sé si os pasó sabes que
were 14 of us screaming like real
éramos 14 gritando como auténticos
gorillas and I understand that for example if I
gorilas y entiendo que por ejemplo si yo
juan didn't like being on the call for long
juan no le molaba estar mucho la llamada
because he wanted to be more arroyo chill with
porque quería estar más arroyo chill con
his streaming not with 14 people
su streaming no con 14 personas
going crazy and then caro maybe there were
volviéndose locos y entonces caro igual
several streams it's because they didn't
hubo varios stream es porque no se
want to join there because the normal thing is to be
querían unir a ahí porque lo normal es
divided into calls of 4 or 5
estar divididos en llamadas de 4 o 5
people and we really got
personas y nosotros la verdad nos
involved  14 fish 14 people the record
metimos 14 pescado 14 personas el disco
people is crazy and more if it's
gente es una locura y más si está
Comanche that Comanche counts for 10 we
comanche que comanche cuenta por 10 os
were 200 okay and chop crazy chef there
éramos 200 vale y picar chef loco
were Comanche and crazy cassette we were
estaban comanche y cassette loco éramos
400 because 14 a little bit although ok
400 porque 14 a un poquito si bien ok
Perez who was Karcher excited that
pérez que estaba karcher excitado que
here it was said suck my dick every
acá se decía comedme la [__] cada
minute me that kid yesterday did not exceed
minuto yo ese chaval ayer no sobrepasó
the truth
la verdad
and then there was Comanche that the stain is
y luego estaba comanche que lo manche es
the pure show
el puro show
and
y
what would many people think I put the
qué pensaría mucha gente yo me metía el
record now yesterday and I was telling
disco ahora ayer y yo me iba contando
new people I mean I was duck I was already
gente nueva o sea yo estaba pato estaba
here there was a lot of people that I didn't even
ya aquí estaba un montón de gente que yo
know was doing this but
ni sabía que estaba haciendo esto pero
I found them and I said [ __ ] great I mean
me los encontré y dije de [__] madre o
between whoever wants the truth and
sea que entre quien quiera la verdad y
friends the truth that I can't say is that
amigos la verdad que no sé decir es que
in fact I am in that record I think I do
de hecho yo estoy en ese disco creo
n't know if I do
no sé si
n't know if it's the same one that I am
no sé si es el mismo en el que yo estoy
but in fact I am in that record I
pero de hecho yo estoy en ese disco
don't have installed yet it's true and
no tengo instalado todavía es verdad y
restorer ordered taste records
restaurador ordenados degustar discos
okay why have I
vale por qué
received the greatest amount of hate and  the
he recibido la mayor cantidad de odio y
harassment that I've received in the 8 years
de acoso que he recibido en los 8 años
that I've been doing things on the internet has
que llevo haciendo cosas de internet ha
been an absolute outrage
sido una auténtica barbaridad
for me it has exceeded all limits
para mí ha superado todos los límites
instead of today they have seen on the internet
que en vez de hoy han visto en internet
sincerely
sinceramente
I have been shocked the truth I mean
me he quedado impactado la verdad o sea
look at the things that have happened to me on the internet they
mira que me han pasado cosas en internet
have insulted me they have said everything to me too
me han insultado me ha dicho de todo
many of course many
también muchos por supuesto muchos
many more good than bad but
muchísimos más buenos que malos pero lo
yesterday was an outrage I mean it's not a
de ayer fue una barbaridad o sea no es
joke yes maybe I've had
broma si a lo mejor he tenido
more than half a million mentions
más de medio millón de menciones
wishing me death of everything a little bit no
deseándome la muerte de todo un poco no
son of a [ __ ] disgusting fat all the
hijo de [__] asqueroso gordo todos los
insults you can think of or so it's
insultos que se os puedan ocurrir o sea
a real beast in fact last
una auténtica animalada de hecho ayer
night I didn't check my phone I mean I
por la noche yo no me del móvil o sea
was with
estaba con
con saba who is the sporting director
con saba que es el director deportivo
of the team I'm chatting for a while and I fell
del equipo estoy charlando un rato y me
asleep this morning he has a ton
dormí hoy por la mañana tiene un montón
of things to do and I had several
de cosas que hacer e tenido varias
meetings because this week is going to be
reuniones porque esta semana va a ser
a very important week and such and I don't know
una semana muy importante y tal y no sé
what and the truth is that he looks at his phone very little
qué y la verdad que mira muy poco el
but the times that I have looked it has
móvil pero las veces que he mirado ha
been an absolute outrage I mean my
sido una auténtica barbaridad o sea mis
mentions are constantly with
menciones son constantemente con gente
French people and it doesn't bother me anymore that they
francesa y ya no me molesta que me
insult me  and that they don't stop because they are not
insulten y que no paren porque no están
stopping for real if this if this that I have
parando de verdad si este si esto que he
received I would have received what kind
recibido yo lo hubiese recibido qué tipo
of
de
audience will this guy from Che
audiencia tendrá el tío de che
Camet have or
camet o
this is the payment
este es el pago
and I
y
think the turkey makes
creo que hace el pavo
videos
videos
what does this man usually do
qué es lo que suele hacer este hombre
all the videos
todos los vídeos
he puts thumbnails
le pone miniaturas
on the
a la
police thumbnail videos of tweets
poli miniatura los vídeos de tweets
or rather what he does is play he will
o sea lo que hace es jugar
have a kind of audience a little girl this
tendrá un tipo de audiencia un poco niña
is the best that has ever been looked for
está lo mejor que se haya puesto a
there it goes there I am not
buscar ahí va ahí no
going to tell you things but the place
voy a decirles cosas pero el sitio sea
was
fue
incredible incredible incredible the one that
increíble increíble increíble la que
fell but each all tells you that it would almost be the
cayó pero cada todas te cuenta que casi
same
que sería lo mismo
so it would be the same from someone who will
así que sería lo mismo de alguien que se
fight the meat things will also have arrived
peleará al cárnico también habrá llegado
I imagine from the
cosas me imagino por parte de la
Spanish community or not we do not know
comunidad española o no no lo sabemos
to Vícam Eto'o is the organizer of
a vícam eto'o es el organizador de
Carmina Corp which is today's rival
carmina corp que es el rival de hoy
[Music] I
[Música]
think that in all sides there are
creo que en todos los bandos hay gente
toxic people well surely the result of
tóxica pues seguramente el resultado de
this one will be because that sense Camet West will
éste será porque ese sentido camet oeste
have a lot of very toxic audience
tendrá mucha audiencia muy tóxica
boxes stop that the camera moves
boxes alto que la cámara se mueva
you notice it there or am I
ustedes lo nota ahí o soy yo que estoy
crazy man I
loco tío
do not know why the camera moves I really do
no sé por qué la cámara se mueve de
not understand  why the camera is moving
no entiendo por qué la cámara se mueve
that sounds I don't understand
eso suena no entiendo
exalting already from the live it's a coffee to
exaltando ya del directo me es un café
make a coffee
crearse un café
and I feel like playing also serious it
y tengo ganas de jugar también graves
's five thirty
son las cinco y media
we play GTA for a while
jugamos un rato al gta
we play a quick algete before I
jugamos un rápido algete antes que me
leave while I have coffee you
vaya mientras me tomar café ti
we play a roller
jugamos un rodillo
yes no
sí no
here
aquí
and then if something happens we come back it is already
y luego si pasa algo volvemos ya se
divided to the main channel about a
divide al canal principal sobre una cosa
chocas thing that I would have done
del chocas que lo hubiera hecho en
live last night but since you go there well it
directo anoche pero como tú ve por ahí
's a video for the main it
pues es un vídeo para principal nos
seems to us that we play
parece que juguemos
Javi practicing not only also like that
javi practicando no sólo también así
man
hombre
don't take it like that I do
no lo toméis así
n't know why the scoreboard says 0 there are
no sé por qué el marcador dice 0 hay
moderators in tweets please
moderadores en tweets por favor que
put that they change the category and the
pongan que cambien la categoría y el
title and everything
título y demás
but why do you have to change the category
pero porque hay que cambiar la categoría
and the [ __ ] title man then it seems that
y el [__] título tío entonces se ve que
I make a shitty title already I know that
hago un título de [__] ya ya sé que
zero comes out on your day live try to
sale cero en tu día vive intentar
update again that I do
actualizar otra vez
n't know why zero comes out look
que no sé por qué sale cero mira
that I don't know why it says zero family
que no sé por qué pone cero familia
that I don't know why zero comes out
que no sé por qué sale cero
[Music]
[Música]
eye ​​I'm
ojo
going to be direct to point out and so
voy a ser directo para señalar y así
if I feel like it I will do it if I feel like it I will
si me da la gana lo haré
Okay, I have
si tengo ganas lo hago vale
to pay, I have to
tengo a pagar
turn it off and turn it back on, man,
tengo apagar y volverlo a encender tío
now you've learned it.
ahora se ha aprendido
Ah,
ah
I
a mí
already want a hamburger, I'm going to
ya tengo ganas de una hamburguesa iré a
sleep, face begging, face begging, face begging,
dormir cara mendigando cara mendigando
now yes, thank you very much,
ahora sí muchas gracias
well
bueno
now why doesn't it go now, it doesn't go to the side,
ahora porque no va
God commands, get out of the way, the
ahora no va al bando dios mando se quite
only God puts it why doesn't it go to the
se pone el solo dios porque no va al
command,
mando
how long are you going live? Well, now I
cuánto tiempo vas en directo pues ahora
have to go and half a half
me tengo que ir y media mitad
[Music]
[Música]
now it's
ahora
put into window mode because
se ha puesto en modo ventana porque
our window models how did you
nuestros modelos ventanas cómo se
get out of window mode, man,
quitaba el modo ventana tío
the Panama cafe, let
el café
's get to it, let's get to it,
vamos al lío
how did you continue in window mode,
como seguiste al modo ventana
like followed, the family window mode
como seguida el modo ventana familiar
at f 4, I can't remember when I entered
al f 4 no caigo al entrar
today, you haven't fooled me.
hoy no me habéis engañado
Hello,
hola
well, here is Paco, Paco, organism, okay, I
bueno aquí está paco paco organismo vale
have to tell you a little about payment,
os tengo que contar un poco sobre pago
the little one, okay, I don't know
el canijo vale
why, I don't
no sé por qué
know, but for some reason in my life,
no sé pero por algún motivo de mi vida
for ccoo, he
para ccoo
appeared here in this, on this side, okay, next to it, he
apareció aquí en este en este lado vale
was, I don't have much idea
al lado estaba ya no tengo mucha idea
why, but well, I pay
del por qué pero bueno pago
for ccoo, the little one
para ccoo el canijo
is a man, okay,
es un hombre le vale
for ccoo, the canine, a man who has a
para ccoo el canino un hombre que tiene
problem, I
problema
pay the canine, daughter had  many problems
pago el can hija tenía muchos problemas
with drugs okay
con las drogas vale
there is because it continues feeling bad that it
hay porque se sigue sintiendo mal que se
continues feeling bad the government
sigue mal el gobierno
you are very bad
ustedes lo muy mal
to know you have to think every
para conocer hay que pensar todos los
day he calls you what he weighs or the [ __ ] notes
días le llama que pesa o el [__] notas
that really [ __ ] stalker piece of [ __ ]
ese de verdad [__] acosador de [__]
or nothing for some reason in life paco
o nada por algún motivo de la vida paco
has appeared here we do not know very well
ha aparecido aquí no sabemos muy bien el
why we do
porqué
not know why but for some reason
no sabemos por qué pero por algún motivo
in life paco appears here paco is
de la vida a paco aparece aquí paco es
a man who is trying to find a
un hombre que está intentando buscar un
place it is not to change the frames per
sitio no es cambiar los frames por
second man
segundo tío
okay wait restart in tweets I'm going to
vale esperar reinicio en tweets me voy a
stay in tweet okay I close on youtube I
quedar en tweet vale cierro en youtube
close on youtube let's go to tweets let's go to
cierro en youtube vamos a tweets vamos a
your saying I'm going to configure it ms and let's go to
tu dicho voy a configurarlo ms y vamos a
tweets close youtube okay close
tweets cierran youtube vale cierran
youtube
youtube
[Music]
[Música]
i
i